Guide to the Time Inc. Life Publishing and Business Records 1936-2001 MS 3009-RG 26
New-York Historical Society
- Series IV. Market Research Department Files, 1938-1970; 5.275 Linear feet in 6 record cartons, 1 flat box
  - Newsstand: Field Organization: Performance Report Procedure, 1955 (Offsite-box 3032, Folder 24)
  - Newsstand: Insert Survey: 1959, undated (Offsite-box 3032, Folder 25)
  - Newsstand: Price Test, 1963-1964 (Offsite-box 3032, Folder 26)
  - Newsstand: Price Test: $0.19 vs. $0.25, 1959 (Offsite-box 3032, Folder 27)
  - Newsstand: Promotion Auxiliary Life Displays, 1952 (Offsite-box 3032, Folder 28)
  - Newsstand: Promotion: Promotion Test in l-list sub-promotion cities, 1955 (Offsite-box 3032, Folder 29)
  - Newsstand: Rate Test: New Mexico and Montana: $0.15 vs. $0.25: 1956 Test, 1956-1957 (Offsite-box 3033, Folder 1-2)
  - Newsstand: Reduced Price Offer, 1962 (Offsite-box 3033, Folder 3)
  - Newsstand: Research Folder, 1962 (Offsite-box 3030, Folder 4-5)
  - Newsstand Sales: Competitive: Effects of, 1960 (Offsite-box 3033, Folder 6)
  - Newsstand Sales: Distribution within Branch Allocation: Urban, 1957 (Offsite-box 3033, Folder 7)
  - Newsstand Sales: Effect of Draw, undated (Offsite-box 3033, Folder 8)
  - Newsstand Sales: Estimates of Issue Sale on Monday and Tuesday, 1955 (Offsite-box 3033, Folder 9)
  - Newsstand Sales: Estimation from Preliminary Checkup, 1957 (Offsite-box 3033, Folder 10)
  - Newsstand Sales: Forecast Trends, 1953-1954 (Offsite-box 3033, Folder 11)
  - Newsstand Sales Charts, undated (Offsite-box 3033, Folder 12)
  - Newsstand Sales of Issues with political cover, 1955 (Offsite-box 3033, Folder 13)
  - Newsstand Sales Research, 1954 (Offsite-box 3033, Folder 14)
  - Newsstand Test on Tuesday Delivery: California, 1961-1962 (Offsite-box 3033, Folder 15)
  - Newsstand Test on Tuesday Delivery: Connecticut, 1961 (Offsite-box 3033, Folder 16)
  - Newsstand Tests: Cover Overlay, 1954-1955 (Offsite-box 3033, Folder 17)
  - Operation Microscope, 1952-1956, 1970, undated (Offsite-box 3033, Folder 18-19)
  - Penetration in Suburbia, 1953 (Offsite-box 3033, Folder 20)
  - Politz: National Study of Newsstand Buyers of Life among Men and Women, 1951 (Offsite-box 3033, Folder 21)
  - Politz: Report on Multiple Experiment to obtain Names and Addresses of Life, 1952-1955 (Offsite-box 3033, Folder 22)
  - Prediction of National Demand, 1958 (Offsite-box 3033, Folder 23)
  - The Problems of Yesteryear, 1938, 1944, undated (Offsite-box 3033, Folder 24)
  - Providence Rack Test, 1954-1955 (Offsite-box 3033, Folder 25)
  - Quality Reading Service: Select Reading Service, 1961, undated (Offsite-box 3033, Folder 26-27)
  - Radio Promotion, 1952-1958 (Offsite-box 3033, Folder 28)
  - Readership Among College Students, undated (Offsite-box 3033, Folder 29)
  - Return as Percent of Draw, 1955 (Offsite-box 3033, Folder 30)
  - Return Percent: Dealers: 1956 Spring, undated (Offsite-box 3033, Folder 31)
  - Return Percent: Distribution Variation in Branches, 1954-1955 (Offsite-box 3033, Folder 32)
  - Sales Quotas, 1952-1954 (Offsite-box 3034, Folder 1)
  - Saturation Tests, 1946-1949 (Offsite-box 3034, Folder 2)
  - Skinner Study: The "Negro" [African-American] Market for Life, 1953 (Offsite-box 3034, Folder 3)
  - S.M: Time, Inc. Newsstand Integration, 1955 (Offsite-box 3034, Folder 4)
  - S.M Consumer Study, 1964-1965 (Offsite-box 3034, Folder 5)
  - S.M Distribution Control, 1954-1956 (Offsite-box 3034, Folder 6)
  - S.M News Company, 1954 (Offsite-box 3034, Folder 7)
  - Small Dealers' Importance, 1955 (Offsite-box 3034, Folder 8)
  - Sports Illustrated: Income Model, 1971 (Offsite-box 3034, Folder 9)
  - Store Survey, undated (Offsite-box 3034, Folder 10)
  - Study of Magazine Readership Among College Students: Gallup, 1967 (Offsite-box 3034, Folder 11)
  - Subscriber - Non-Subscriber Survey: Politz, 1950 (Offsite-box 3034, Folder 12)
  - Subscriber Check: Dallas, 1959 (Offsite-box 3034, Folder 13)
  - Subscribers' Attitudes to Time and Life Magazines, 1963 (Offsite-box 3034, Folder 14)
  - Subscriptions: New General Mailing Plans: 1953-1955, 1952-1954 (Offsite-box 3034, Folder 15)
  - Subscriptions Committee, 1954-1955 (Offsite-box 3034, Folder 16)
  - Supplements, 1968-1970 (Offsite-box 3034, Folder 17)
  - Supplements: Age Groups, 1969 (Offsite-box 3034, Folder 18)
  - Supplements: Eisenberg Meeting with RHO, RJS, OG, 1970 (Offsite-box 3034, Folder 19)
  - Supplements: Food, 1969-1970 (Offsite-box 3034, Folder 20)
  - Supplements: Movies, 1970 (Offsite-box 3034, Folder 21)
  - Supplements: Travel, 1969 (Offsite-box 3034, Folder 22)
  - Supplements: TV, 1968-1969 (Offsite-box 3034, Folder 23-24)
  - Television Effect on Life Circulation, 1951-1952 (Offsite-box 3034, Folder 25)
  - Time Inc. Stockholders Report, 1965 (Offsite-box 3034, Folder 26)
- Series V. Advertising Copy Acceptance Files, 1946-1975; 0.35 Linear feet in 3 record cartons
  While the Advertising Copy Acceptance department is believed to have existed since the beginning of Life, it is unclear which department it resided in. The first time that the department is listed in the department heads list for Time Inc. is in 1964. Prior this point, the department could have been part of Advertising Sales or the department known as Makeup and Advertising Records which only appeared in the department heads list from 1960 to 1962.
  The Advertising Copy Acceptance Files covers the period of 1946 to 1975 and focuses editing and approving the text that would appear in ads featured in Life. Included in this series are clippings and correspondence. The correspondence discusses the use of ads, the text to be included in ads, complaints about ads, and changes to be made to ads.
  - Greystone Press, 1949-1956, 1962-1965, 1972 (Offsite-box 3034, Folder 27-28)
  - Greystone Press [RESTRICTED], 1973 (Offsite-box R27)
  - Grolier, 1946-1951, 1960-1975 (Offsite-box 3035, Folder 1-3)
  - Grolier [RESTRICTED], 1962 (Offsite-box R27)
  - IBM, 1956-1959 (Offsite-box 3035, Folder 4)
  - Innerspace Environments, Inc.: Waterbeds, 1972-1975 (Offsite-box 3035, Folder 5)
- Series VI. Marketing and Sales Files, 1967, circa 1986; 1.55 Linear feet in 1 record carton, 1 flat box
  The Marketing and Sales Files consists of two binders. The "Facts of Life" binder contains memoranda and reports sent to Sam Wilson, a salesman, and includes data about circulation, audiences, subscribers, newsstand sales, advertising pages and revenues, rates, and production. These records seem to relate more to sales of the magazine rather than sales of advertising although it could be about ad sales. The materials in the binder have been rehoused in folders, and the binder cover retained separately.
  The 1967 binder does not have a title, but includes information about Life's editorial aims and examples of the materials in Life. It looks like these were used to market the magazine.
  - "Facts of Life" Papers, circa 1986 (Offsite-box 3035, Folder 6-10)
  - "Facts of Life" Binder Cover, circa 1986 (Offsite-box 3036)
  - Life Editorial Aims, Communication, and Advertising, 1967 (Offsite-box 3040, Folder 1)
- Series VII. Public Relations Department Files, 1978-1998; 0.25 Linear feet in 1 record carton
  The Public Relations Department files cover the period of 1978 to 1998 and focus on exhibits as well as mentions of Time Inc. in the media. The files concerning exhibits are have two separate focuses. One of the focuses is on exhibits created for Alfred Eisenstaedt and the other is on images and photos featured in Life. The Eisenstaedt exhibit appears to have been created by Life while the exhibit of Life appears to be created by an outside organization. Included in this series are clippings, press releases, photographs, notes, and correspondence discussing exhibits, reproductions, and the use of photographs.
  - Eisenstaedt, Alfred, 1978-1995 (Offsite-box 3035, Folder 11-14)
  - Life Exhibits, 1986-1988 (Offsite-box 3035, Folder 15)
  - Time Warner in the News, 1998 (Offsite-box 3035, Folder 16)
- Series VIII. Circulation Director Files, 1961-1976; 6 Linear feet in 6 record cartons
  The Circulation Director Files contain records from several different directors with the majority from Bruce Barnet who was the final Circulation Director before the suspension of Life in 1972.
  Organized into two subseries:
  Subseries VIII.A. General Files
  Subseries VIII.B. Bruce Barnet Files
  - Subseries VIII.A. General Files, 1961-1972; 0.33 Linear feet in 6 folders
    Includes a mix of files from several Life circulation directors: John Watters, William Conway, Robert Moore, and Bruce Barnet.
    Organized alphabetically. Order was imposed by the archivist.
    - Life Atlantic, 1968-1969 (Offsite-box 3819, Folder 1)
    - Life South Pacific, 1968 (Offsite-box 3819, Folder 2)
    - Military Sale and Distribution (Vietnam), 1965-1966 (Offsite-box 3819, Folder 3)
    - Publishers Clearing House, 1961-1972 (Offsite-box 3819, Folder 4-5)
    - Rate Tests, 1965-1970 (Offsite-box 3819, Folder 6)
  - Subseries VIII.B. Bruce Barnet Files, 1963-1976; 5.67 Linear feet in 7 record cartons
    Bruce Barnet was the final Circulation Director for Life before publication was suspended at the end of 1972. Based on his records, he may have joined Life in mid-1972 and stayed on through 1973 to close out business. After finishing his work with Life, Barnet transferred to Sports Illustrated to serve as Circulation Director. For the rest of his career at Time Inc., he held positions in Corporate Circulation and the Magazine Development Group and served as the Magazine Group Vice President of Planning.
    Bruce Barnet's files document his short term as Life Circulation Director during the final months of publication and after publication was suspended. His files include some materials from earlier years that may have been used by him as reference. His records document some evaluation of the financial issues of Life and the slowness of subscription refunds and subscription transfers including a lawsuit regarding these problems.
    Arranged alphabetically based on the original order. Files from several boxes have been interfiled together as they all contain records from Barnet.
    - Accounting, 1972 (Offsite-box 3819, Folder 7)
    - Acknowledgments, 1973 (Offsite-box 3035, Folder 8)
    - Agency, 1972-1974 (Offsite-box 3819, Folder 9-12)
    - Agency: School Plans, 1972 (Offsite-box 3819, Folder 13)
    - Agency: Williard Brown, 1972 (Offsite-box 3819, Folder 14)
    - Agents, 1972 (Offsite-box 3819, Folder 15)
    - Announcements, 1972 (Offsite-box 3819, Folder 16)
    - Annual Meeting, 1973 (Offsite-box 3819, Folder 17)
    - APO/FPO, 1973 (Offsite-box 3819, Folder 18)
    - Attorney General [empty], undated (Offsite-box 3819, Folder 19)
    - Audit Bureau of Circulation, 1969-1975 (Offsite-box 3819, Folder 20-22)
    - Back Issues, 1972-1973 (Offsite-box 3819, Folder 23)
    - Best of Life, 1972-1973 (Offsite-box 3819, Folder 24)
    - Bill Flyers, 1972 (Offsite-box 3819, Folder 25)
    - Bills, 1972-1973 (Offsite-box 3819, Folder 26-28)
    - Budget, 1966 (Offsite-box 3037, Folder 1)
    - Bulk, 1972-1974 (Offsite-box 3037, Folder 2)
    - Cage, 1973 (Offsite-box 3037, Folder 3)
    - Canada, 1973 (Offsite-box 3037, Folder 4)
    - Cash Refunds, 1973-1974 (Offsite-box 3037, Folder 5)
    - Change of Address, 1973 (Offsite-box 3037, Folder 6)
    - Christmas, 1972, undated (Offsite-box 3037, Folder 7-8)
    - Circulation: Deadlines, 1972 (Offsite-box 3037, Folder 9)
    - Circulation: Statistics, 1972 (Offsite-box 3037, Folder 10)
    - Circulation: Venezuela: Affidavit, 1976 (Offsite-box 3037, Folder 11)
    - Competitor's Promotion, circa 1970 (Offsite-box 3037, Folder 12)
    - Complaints, 1972-1973 (Offsite-box 3037, Folder 13-14)
    - Complaint Form Letters, 1973-1975 (Offsite-box 3037, Folder 15)
    - Complaint Reports, 1973-1974 (Offsite-box 3037, Folder 16-19)
    - Computing Forecasting, 1969-1972 (Offsite-box 3037, Folder 20)
    - Consolidation, 1972 (Offsite-box 3037, Folder 21)
    - Conversion Method [empty], undated (Offsite-box 3037, Folder 22)
    - Copy Rate, 1972 (Offsite-box 3037, Folder 23)
    - Corporate Advertising, 1972 (Offsite-box 3037, Folder 24)
    - Corporate Circulation Presentation, 1972 (Offsite-box 3037, Folder 25)
    - Corporate Television Test, 1972 (Offsite-box 3037, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence, 1973 (Offsite-box 3037, Folder 27)
    - Cover Test, 1972 (Offsite-box 3037, Folder 28)
    - Cowin, Bob, 1972 (Offsite-box 3037, Folder 29)
    - Deferred Income, 1972 (Offsite-box 3037, Folder 30-31)
    - Delivery, 1972 (Offsite-box 3038, Folder 1)
    - Dialogue Marketing Inc. (DMI), 1972-1973 (Offsite-box 3038, Folder 2-4)
    - Direct Mail, 1972 (Offsite-box 3038, Folder 5-8)
    - Direct Renewal Report, 1972 (Offsite-box 3038, Folder 9)
    - Distribution, 1972 (Offsite-box 3038, Folder 10)
    - Domestic Foreign Newsstand, 1973 (Offsite-box 3038, Folder 11)
    - Downe Communications, 1972 (Offsite-box 3038, Folder 12)
    - Duplicate Copies, 1972 (Offsite-box 3038, Folder 13)
    - Edit Survey, 1972 (Offsite-box 3038, Folder 14)
    - Employees, 1972-1973 (Offsite-box 3038, Folder 15)
    - Evaluation, 1972 (Offsite-box 3038, Folder 16)
    - Executive Voice, 1973 (Offsite-box 3038, Folder 17-18)
    - File Maintenance Tapes, 1973 (Offsite-box 3038, Folder 19)
    - Filler Ads, 1972 (Offsite-box 3038, Folder 20)
    - 541 (Chicago offices), 1972 (Offsite-box 3038, Folder 21-24)
    - For the Record, 1973 (Offsite-box 3038, Folder 25)
    - FPS, 1973-1974 (Offsite-box 3038, Folder 26)
    - FTC [empty], undated (Offsite-box 3038, Folder 27)
    - Fulfillment, 1972-1973 (Offsite-box 3038, Folder 28-29)
    - Geographics, 1972 (Offsite-box 3038, Folder 30)
    - Grace, 1972 (Offsite-box 3038, Folder 31)
    - Income, 1972 (Offsite-box 3038, Folder 32)
    - Inserts, 1972 (Offsite-box 3038, Folder 33-34)
    - Insert Allocations, 1972 (Offsite-box 3038, Folder 35)
    - Inserts: Combo Test, 1972 (Offsite-box 3038, Folder 36)
    - Installment Billing, 1972 (Offsite-box 3038, Folder 37)
    - International, 1972-1974 (Offsite-box 3038, Folder 38)
    - International Fees, 1972 (Offsite-box 3038, Folder 39-40)
    - International Newsstand, 1972 (Offsite-box 3038, Folder 41)
    - International Subs, 1972 (Offsite-box 3038, Folder 42)
    - Inventory and Analysis, 1972-1973 (Offsite-box 3038, Folder 43-44)
    - Issue Dates, 1972 (Offsite-box 3038, Folder 45)
    - Keys / Media, 1972 (Offsite-box 3038, Folder 46)
    - Kipperman vs, Time, 1973-1974 (Offsite-box 3038, Folder 47)
    - Last Issue, 1972-1973 (Offsite-box 3038, Folder 48)
    - Lawsuit: Mr. S. Josel, 1973-1974 (Offsite-box 3038, Folder 49-51)
    - Liability [empty], undated (Offsite-box 3038, Folder 52)
    - Liability Reports, 1973-1974 (Offsite-box 3038, Folder 53)
    - Lieberman Study, 1972 (Offsite-box 3038, Folder 54)
    - Limbo Tape, 1973 (Offsite-box 3038, Folder 55)
    - List Rental, 1972-1973 (Offsite-box 3038, Folder 56-57)
    - Magazine Conversion Methods [empty], undated (Offsite-box 3038, Folder 58)
    - Magazine Publisher's Association (MPA), 1973 (Offsite-box 3038, Folder 59)
    - Mailings, 1973 (Offsite-box 3038, Folder 60-61)
    - Marketing, 1972 (Offsite-box 3820, Folder 1)
    - Master File, 1973 (Offsite-box 3820, Folder 2)
    - Media, 1972-1973 (Offsite-box 3820, Folder 3-4)
    - Media: Beetleboard, 1972? (Offsite-box 3820, Folder 5)
    - Media: Buying, 1972 (Offsite-box 3820, Folder 6)
    - Media Returns, 1971 (Offsite-box 3820, Folder 7)
    - Media: Three Way Combo, 1972 (Offsite-box 3820, Folder 8)
    - Media Trades, 1972 (Offsite-box 3820, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaenous, 1972-1973 (Offsite-box 3820, Folder 10)
    - Monthly Complaint Report, 1972 (Offsite-box 3820, Folder 11)
    - Monthly Report: Life, 1972 (Offsite-box 3820, Folder 12)
    - Monthly Report: Other Magazines, 1972 (Offsite-box 3820, Folder 13)
    - Motivation Analysis, 1972 (Offsite-box 3820, Folder 14)
    - Net Paid: Life, 1972 (Offsite-box 3820, Folder 15)
    - New Business, 1972-1973 (Offsite-box 3820, Folder 16-17)
    - Newspaper Stuffers, 1972 (Offsite-box 3820, Folder 18)
    - Newsstand, 1971-1973 (Offsite-box 3820, Folder 19-21)
    - Newsstand Delivery, 1972 (Offsite-box 3820, Folder 22)
    - Newsstand: Newspaper Co-op, 1972 (Offsite-box 3820, Folder 23)
    - New York State Attorney General, 1973 (Offsite-box 3820, Folder 24)
    - Notification: Charge Donors, circa 1973 (Offsite-box 3820, Folder 25)
    - Notification: Gifts, circa 1973 (Offsite-box 3820, Folder 26)
    - Notification: Non-Respondents, 1973-1974 (Offsite-box 3820, Folder 27-28)
    - Notification: Paid Donors, circa 1973 (Offsite-box 3820, Folder 29)
    - Obsolete Stock, 1973 (Offsite-box 3820, Folder 30)
    - Operating Costs: 1973 Estimate, 1972 (Offsite-box 3820, Folder 31-32)
    - Operating Costs: Original Budgets, 1963, 1969, 1971 (Offsite-box 3820, Folder 33-35)
    - Operating Statement, 1972 (Offsite-box 3820, Folder 36)
    - Option Code Numbers, undated (Offsite-box 3820, Folder 37)
    - Option Processing Report, 1973-1974 (Offsite-box 3820, Folder 38-40)
    - Outside Publishers, 1974 (Offsite-box 3820, Folder 41)
    - Overstock, 1973 (Offsite-box 3820, Folder 42)
    - Perle, Gabe, 1972 (Offsite-box 3820, Folder 43)
    - Personnel, undated (Offsite-box 3820, Folder 44)
    - Premiums, 1972 (Offsite-box 3820, Folder 45)
    - Price Commission, 1971-1972 (Offsite-box 3039, Folder 1-2)
    - Processing, 1973 (Offsite-box 3039, Folder 3)
    - Publicity, 1973-1974 (Offsite-box 3039, Folder 4)
    - Publicity [RESTRICTED], 1973 (Offsite-box R27)
      Includes audiovisual material:
      1 audiotape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, stereo; 7 in., 1/4 in. tape. On label attached to reel: "Tape Transcription Card Series Title W-O-S-U Radio Ombudsman Service Program Title Life Magazine Subscription Participants Listener, Bruce Barnett, Ron Wolf Speed 7 1/2 Open cue Aired 9-10-73".
    - Publishers Clearing House, 1972-1973 (Offsite-box 3039, Folder 5)
    - Quantities Mailed, undated (Offsite-box 3039, Folder 6)
    - Reilly, Bob, 1973 (Offsite-box 3039, Folder 7)
    - Reprints, 1973 (Offsite-box 3039, Folder 8)
    - Request Nothing, 1973 (Offsite-box 3039, Folder 9)
    - Response by Preferential Order, 1973 (Offsite-box 3039, Folder 10)
    - Returns, 1973-1974 (Offsite-box 3039, Folder 11-14)
    - R. G. Meadows Inc., 1972 (Offsite-box 3039, Folder 15)
    - School Plans, 1972-1973 (Offsite-box 3039, Folder 16)
    - Second Mailing, 1973 (Offsite-box 3039, Folder 17)
    - Selection, 1973 (Offsite-box 3039, Folder 18)
    - Special Lists, 1972-1973 (Offsite-box 3039, Folder 19)
    - Special Report: 1974, 1973 (Offsite-box 3039, Folder 20)
    - Special Report: Spirit of Israel, 1973 (Offsite-box 3039, Folder 21)
    - Sports Illustrated Games, 1973 (Offsite-box 3039, Folder 22)
    - Statistical Reports, 1972 (Offsite-box 3039, Folder 23)
    - Statistical Tracking, 1973 (Offsite-box 3039, Folder 24)
    - Stockholders, 1973 (Offsite-box 3039, Folder 25)
    - Suspends, 1973 (Offsite-box 3039, Folder 26)
    - Suspension Reports, 1974 (Offsite-box 3039, Folder 27)
    - Third Mailing, 1973-1974 (Offsite-box 3039, Folder 28)
    - Time Inc. Magazines, 1972-1973 (Offsite-box 3039, Folder 29)
    - Time Zip Analysis, 1973 (Offsite-box 3039, Folder 30)
    - Tracking, 1973 (Offsite-box 3039, Folder 31)
    - Transfers, 1973 (Offsite-box 3039, Folder 32)
    - Unprocessed Mail, 1972 (Offsite-box 3039, Folder 33)
    - Updater, 1973 (Offsite-box 3039, Folder 34)
    - Venture, 1973 (Offsite-box 3039, Folder 35)
    - Weekly Option Report: Second Mailing, 1972-1974 (Offsite-box 3039, Folder 36)
- Series IX: Newsstand Department Records, 1949-1967; 1.5 Linear feet in 2 record cartons, 1 flat box
  Biographical / Historical
  According to a memorandum transferring the files to the Time Inc. Archives, these files are part of the Newsstand Department, which was retail sales, with several regarding the Retail Auxilliary Display Program. This program seems to be managed by the Newsstand Department.
  Newsstand Department Records include materials on the placement and sale of Life from store displays, not subscribers.
  - Archives Transfer Memorandum, 1967 (Offsite-box 3320, Folder 1)
  - Cover Flap: Bonus Book Offer, 1965-1966 (Offsite-box 3320, Folder 2)
  - Magazine Merchandising, 1954 (Offsite-box 3320, Folder 3)
  - Newsstand Convention: Photobooks, 1949-1953 (Offsite-box 3320, Folder 4-5)
  - Panorama and Accompanying Poster: "Changing the Way of the Plains", undated (Offsite-box 3320, Item 1-2)
  - Retail Auxiliary Display Program: General, 1957 (Offsite-box 3320, Folder 6)
  - Retail Auxiliary Display Program: General, 1954-1955 (Offsite-box 3325, Folder 6)
  - Retail Auxiliary Display Program: Contracts [RESTRICTED], 1957-1959; 1.5 Linear feet (2 boxes) (Offsite-box R56)
  - Time Capsule, 1962 (Offsite-box 3320, Item 3)
    Silver cardboard cylinder containing March 1962 issues featuring John Glenn and a letter to Life salesmen.